{"game_code":"69J1QYC4","level_name":"a","questions":[{"answer":"Data","incorrect":["Information","Files","Knowledge"],"question":"This is the basic building block of information, and it becomes meaningful when processed or interpreted."},{"answer":"It is raw and unprocessed","incorrect":["It is easily understood","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"What is the primary characteristic of data?"},{"answer":"Information is derived from processing and organizing data","incorrect":["Information is always in a raw and unprocessed state","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"Which of the following statements is true about information?"},{"answer":"Network topology","incorrect":["Network cables","Network design","Network model"],"question":"The arrangement of computers, cables, and other components on a network."},{"answer":"Bus Topology","incorrect":["Star Topology","Ring Topology","Mesh Topology"],"question":"Consists of numbers of computers in a row connected by a single cable segment called trunk, also known as backbone or segment."},{"answer":"Ring Topology","incorrect":["Star Topology","Bus Topology","Mesh Topology"],"question":"This topology provides a reliable signal that can travel large network because the signal is regenerated by each workstation when passed on to its neighbor."},{"answer":"Star Topology","incorrect":["Ring Topology","Bus Topology","Mesh Topology"],"question":"This topology is used to connect computers in a workgroup or departmental local area network (LAN) using a hub. It can also be used to connect workgroup or departmental hubs using a master hub or switch."},{"answer":"Mesh Topology","incorrect":["Ring Topology","Bus Topology","Star Topology"],"question":"A network topology in which additional networking components are used to provide redundant data paths."},{"answer":"Full Mesh Topology","incorrect":["Partial Mesh Topology","Bus Topology","Star Topology"],"question":"It provides a direct link between each pair of nodes on the backbone network."},{"answer":"Partial Mesh Topology","incorrect":["Full Mesh Topology","Bus Topology","Star Topology"],"question":"This only includes some redundant data paths to provide some level of fault tolerance."},{"answer":"A segment cable fault affects all workstations","incorrect":["Bus Topology is easy to implement.","It is easy to extend","Low cost"],"question":"Which of the following is the disadvantage of Bus topology?"},{"answer":"Centralized network/hub monitoring","incorrect":["Hub can be a single point of failure","Hubs are slightly more expensive than thin-Ethernet","Requires more cable than most other topologies"],"question":"All of these are disadvantages of Star topology except?"}],"time":71}